Lionel Andres Messi
莱昂内尔·安德烈斯·梅西
Hailed by football enthusiasts, analysts, and even fellow professionals as the greatest footballer to ever play the sport.
被足球爱好者、分析师，甚至同行职业球员誉为有史以来最伟大的足球运动员。
【Spanish】
有人告诉我："我看过贝利踢球，我看过马拉多纳踢球，我也可以说，我看过里奥·梅西踢球。"There are people who tell me, I saw Pelé play, I saw Maradona play, I can say that I saw Leo Messi play.
He doesn't have the ball. It's unbelievable the character, how he plays, how he works for the team. He's one of the gods of football.
他脚下没有球的时候也是如此出色。他的品格、踢球方式以及为球队付出的精神都令人难以置信。他就是足球界的传奇人物之一。
He has achieved a groundbreaking six Ballon d'Or awards, six European Golden Shoes, and holds records for the most goals and assists in La Liga history.
他获得了创纪录的六座金球奖、六座欧洲金靴奖，并保持着西甲历史进球数和助攻数最多的纪录。
【Spanish】
这项荣誉更多属于整个团队，而不仅仅属于我个人，因为很多进球并不是我一个人的功劳。It's an award for the group, more than individually, because there are a lot of goals and I just didn't get it.
Diagnosed with a medical condition at just 11 years old that could have derailed his career before it even started, Messi defied expectations and stunned the world with his extraordinary footballing talent.
梅西在年仅11岁时便被诊断出患有一种可能让他的职业生涯尚未开始就夭折的疾病，但他打破了所有人的预期，并凭借非凡的足球天赋震惊了世界。
Statistics and history go out the window, the way he's playing.
按照他现在这种踢法，数据和历史纪录都显得无关紧要了。
Experience the journey of one of football's most legendary figures, and delve into the story of Argentina's footballing icon.
一起踏上足球史上最具传奇色彩人物之一的旅程，深入了解这位阿根廷足球偶像的故事。
【Spanish】
我成长了，也学到了很多，现在我仍然努力不断丰富自己的足球水平。I grew up, I learned a lot, and now I try to keep adding things to my football.
This is the mesmerizing tale of Lionel Messi.
这就是莱昂内尔·梅西令人着迷的传奇故事。